listsconnect.com 2014-11-22

# ListsConnect.com - Profitable Email Marketing

**Terms and Conditions**

**Acceptance of Terms**

This Agreement contains the complete terms and conditions that apply to your participation in our site. If you wish to use the site including its tools and services please read these terms of use carefully. By accessing this site or using any part of the site or any content or services hereof, you agree to become bound by these terms and conditions. If you do not agree to all the terms and conditions, then you may not access the site or use the content or any services in the site.

**Modifications of Terms of Use**

Amendments to this agreement can be made and effected by us from time to time without specific notice to your end. Agreement posted on the Site reflects the latest agreement and you should carefully review the same before you use our site.

**Use of the Site**

The Site allows you to post offers, advertise, send e-mail ads to list members and purchase online. However, you are prohibited to do the following acts, to wit: (a) use our sites, including its services and or tools if you are not able to form legally binding contracts, are under the age of 18, or are temporarily or indefinitely suspended from using our sites, services, or tools (b) posting of an items in inappropriate category or areas on our sites and services; (c) collecting information about users’ personal information; (d) maneuvering the price of any item or interfere with other users' listings; (f) post false, inaccurate, misleading, defamatory, or libelous content; (g) take any action that may cause malfunctioning of our site.

 **Registration Information**

For you to complete the sign-up process in our site, you must provide your full legal name, a valid email address, username and password in order to complete the signup process. You must qualify that you are 18 years or older and must be responsible for keeping your password secure and be responsible for all activities under your account. You must not transmit any worms or viruses or any code of a destructive nature. Any information provided by you or gathered by the site or third parties during any visit to the site shall be subject to the terms of ListsConnect.com’s Privacy Policy.

**Age Limit**

You agree that you are the age of 18 or older. If you join and are not 18 years old, we hold the right to terminate your account without a refund. You may be contacted for age verification purposes and agree to prove you meet the age requirement with legal documentation.

**Number of Accounts**

You agree to only create one (1) account in ListsConnect.com

**Emails**

As a member of ListsConnect.com you agree to automatically receive emails from administration, owners and from other members. These emails include a few addresses, bounce@listsconnect.com, member.noreply@listsconnect.com, and admin.noreply@listsconnect.com. Add these to your whitelist as these emails are not spam. By taking this step it ensures you'll receive admin updates, announcements, and important information as well as member emails. You may also receive emails from ListsConnect.com owners.

**Email Contents**

All emails sent by members may not include pornography of any kind, gambling, viruses or links to viruses, warez, malware, spyware, or other innappropriate sites. These are subject to being deleted and the sender's account terminated without refund or warning. You agree emails not to be hateful, profane, racists, prejudice or crime related. You agree emails will be free of supporting or promoting illegal activity and that the emails follow as well as comply with federal and state laws. You agree to keep all emails and messages honest without misleading information. You agree emails will contain links that do not break frames disrupting the functionality of ListsConnect.com.

**Autoresponders and Bounced Emails**

If your email address bounces, send back or reject emails sent to you put your ListsConnect.com account at risk of suspension or termination. ListsConnect.com will allow you to contact us if your account has been suspended but requires proof of any upgrade. If such is the case, you need to supply Listsconnect.com support with transaction number in order to have your account reactivated. Earnings, commissions and referrals may be lost for suspended accounts.

**Refund Policy**

All payments, membership costs and subscriptions are non-refundable. Due to the nature of this service, commissions are credited to your sponsor automatically and can not be returned to you. The removal or deletion of your account on your own terms will result in a loss of any earning balance within your account and therefore remove the possibility of payment.

Removing your account in ListsConnect.com will NOT cancel your PayPal, or related subscriptions. You are responsible for canceling or managing any 3rd party payment systems. If you write a support ticket and provide your subscription information, such as a recent transaction ID or subscription number, we can cancel these for you.. we can not cancel your subscriptions without this information. Always refer to your PayPal to ensure accuracy, we do not bill you, you control the billing through PayPal.

**Earning Credits**

Earning credits falsely by trying to misuse or exploit ListsConnect.com is strictly prohibited. By not following this policy your account will be suspended or terminated without a refund. All credits, whether purchased or earned, will be deducted from your account without warning.

**Regulations, Rules and Policies**

Owners, administrators and support of ListsConnect.com hold the right to make final decisions of policies, regulations and rules, and reserve the right to make any modifications, change, add or remove rules and policies as seen fit at any time for any reason. You agree to not hold ListsConnect.com and owners liable for rules and policies or any items related to the membership and service.

**Term**

This Agreement will remain in full force and effect while you use the Website. You may terminate your membership at any time for any reason by following the instructions on the “DELETE ACCOUNT” in the "My Account" page. We may terminate your membership for any reason at any time. If you are using a paid version of the Service and we terminate your membership in the Service because you have breached this Agreement, you will not be entitled to any refund of unused subscription fees. Even after your membership is terminated, certain sections of this Agreement will remain in effect.

**Links to Other Sites**

This site contains links to other sites. This site is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other web sites.

**Liability**

ListsConnect.com is an information marketing tool used to help it's members on the Internet. ListsConnect.com does not make any promises written or implied as to the amount of money that can be made from ListsConnect.com. It is your responsibility to make sure your payment email address is correct. Commission payments made to the wrong account because of an incorrectly entered addresses/accounts is your responsibility.

**Confidentiality**

You agree not to disclose information you obtain from us and or from our clients, advertisers and members. All information submitted to by an end-user customer pursuant to a Program is proprietary information of ListsConnect.com. Such customer information is confidential and may not be disclosed. Members agrees not to reproduce, disseminate, sell, distribute or commercially exploit any such proprietary information in any manner.

**Non-Assignment of Rights**

Your rights of whatever nature cannot be assigned nor transferred to anybody, and any such attempt may result in termination of this Agreement, without liability to us. However, we may assign this Agreement to any person at any time without notice.

**Waiver**

Failure of the ListsConnect.com to insist upon strict performance of any of the terms, conditions and covenants hereof shall not be deemed a relinquishment or waiver of any rights or remedy that the we may have, nor shall it be construed as a waiver of any subsequent breach of the terms, conditions or covenants hereof, which terms, conditions and covenants shall continue to be in full force and effect.

**and Severability of Terms.**

In the event that any provision of these Terms and Conditions is found invalid or unenforceable pursuant to any judicial decree or decision, such provision shall be deemed to apply only to the maximum extent permitted by law, and the remainder of these Terms and Conditions shall remain valid and enforceable according to its terms.

**Entire Agreement**

This Agreement shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the substantive laws of Philippines, without any reference to conflict-of-laws principles. The Agreement describes and encompasses the entire agreement between us and you, and supersedes all prior or contemporaneous agreements, representations, warranties and understandings with respect to the Site, the contents and materials provided by or through the Site, and the subject matter of this Agreement.

**Choice of Law; Jurisdiction; Forum**

Any dispute, controversy or difference which may arise between the parties out of, in relation to or in connection with this Agreement is hereby irrevocably submitted to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of Philippines, to the exclusion of any other courts without giving effect to its conflict of laws provisions or your actual state or country of residence.

**Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which ListsConnect.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the www.listsconnect.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by ListsConnect.com.

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**Javascript**

Our site may use JavaScript to improve site design, aid user-interaction and validate forms. Your browser must support JavaScript so that our site will function properly.

**How we use collected information**

Information obtained about you for the purpose of creating your ListsConnect.com account shall be used only for the purpose of maintaining and updating your membership, as well as direct email contact from ListsConnect.com. You will receive member mailings from other members as a member, however these mailings are sent through the system and the senders do not have access to your actual e-mail address. You are free to remove your account and stop receiving member mailings at any time. You also have the ability to send member mailings to list members of our membership.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Contests**

We run contests on this site in which we ask users for contact information (such as their name and email address). The user's contact information is used to contact the user when necessary, such as if they win a contest or to notify users of upcoming contests.

**Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

ListsConnect.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact our support.

This document was last updated on May 09, 2012
